

jza255@sfu.ca Vancouver, BC

Design Portfolio

INDUSTRY EXPERIENCE

Digital Communications Assistant

Fisheries and Oceans Canada

January 2023 - April 2023

- Created, managed, and updated the intranet and official government sites, which includes coding HTML using Adobe Dreamweaver and Drupal with consideration for accessibility for the general public.
- Designed graphics for the International Women's Day campaign using Adobe InDesign and Photoshop, which were posted on official social media accounts.
- Participated as communications support for a high-profile international marine conference with up to 3000 visitors, photographing the venue and visitors to create content for the social media pages.

Commission Illustrator

Freelance

October 2020 - Present

- Created digital illustrations for customers through means of commission from social media platforms.
- Clearly **communicated** with the customers and **accommodated** their ideas with my own interpretations.

DESIGN EXPERIENCE

Editorial Designer

Orbit Magazine - Academic Project

May 2023 - June 2023

- Created a magazine from branding to researching about potential readerships.
- Used Adobe InDesign and Photoshop to create essential parts of magazine from cover, table of contents, and editorial feature. Used Figma for web mockup.

UX/UI Designer

Con-TACT - Academic Project

January 2022 - April 2022

 Conducted user research, ideated core features, wireframed, and designed high-fidelity UI and prototype interactions for a convention planning app within a team of 3.

PROFILE

As a passionate designer, I bring a unique blend of **creativity and technical expertise** to every project I undertake. With a keen eye for detail and a deep understanding of **user experience principles**, I strive to create **intuitive** and **visually appealing** designs that elevate the overall product experience.

SKILLS

Design Tools

Experienced in using digital softwares such as Figma, Clip Studio Paint, UXPin, Adobe Photoshop, Indesign, Illustrator, After Effects.

Design Deliverable

Figma Components, Wireframes, Interaction Flows, Sketching, User Journey Maps, Personas, Usability Testing, Prototypes.

Programming Languages

Experienced in coding including HTML, CSS, Java, JavaScript, and Python.

EDUCATION

Simon Fraser University

Bachelor of Arts

September 2019 - Present

Undergraduate student majoring in Interactive Arts and Technology with concentration in design.

LaSalle College

S.W.E.A.T. Program

March 2019

Participated in hands-on workshops in graphic design, learning to use various Adobe Cloud softwares in a collaborative process.